CONTACT

Phone

+11 230 909 8298

Email

peterson2020@fakeemail.com

Address

30 Rockefeller Plaza, NewYork, NY

EDUCATION

University of Kwazulu-Natal

Bachelor of Computer Science and Information Technogies

July 2015 - Nov 2017

University of Kwazulu-Natal

Bachelor of Computer Science
Honours

November 2018 - Present

SKILL

- JAVA
- PYTHON
- C++
- C#
- RUBY

hei now Peterson

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

ABOUT ME

Results driven individual with four years experience desiring to bring engineering and telecommunication experience to a software engineering position at ABC Company. Searching for the oppotunirt to bring 8+ years experience, and server maintenance to a software engineer position with ABC Company incorporating critical thinking, problem solving and leadership

EXPERIENCE

BACK-END DEVELOPER

Shakinah Sports

January 2017 - August 2017

A company that rents out stadiums for sports or entertainment purposes.

- Facilitate back-end aspect of things
- Make sure everything was insynch with everything
- Communicate well with the front end stuff
- Make sure data storage and app is in synch

IT INTERNSHIP

Central Transport Organisation

July 2019 - Present

A government parastatal that procures, maintains and services state owned vehicles

- Mantain server
- Provide and facilitate end user assistance
- Maintain computer parifinalia
- Make sure data storage and app is in synch

EDUCATION

University of Kwazulu-Natal

July 2015 - Nov 2017

Bachelor of Computer Science and Information Technlogies

University of Kwazulu-Natal

November 2018

Bachelor of Computer Science Honours

- Javascript
- HTML
- CSS
- Angular JSNode.js